Finding aid for the Karl G. Yoneda papers, 1892-1998, bulk 1925-1989 LSC.1592
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 3. Military Services of Japanese Americans, 1940-1995, bulk 1944-1950
  - 3.1 Office of the War Information Psychological Warfare Team, the China- Burma-India Office, 1940-1995, bulk 1944-1950
    - Propaganda Materials and Booklets (6 of 6), 1944 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      One scrapbook titled: Leaflets in Japanese, Book C, with a label, "Psychological Warfare Team U.S.O.W.I. A.P.O. 689 I.B.T Book no. 21 issued to T/3 Karl Yoneda 18184307." Dated on March, 1944. Contains propaganda materials, such as ?? dentan [= airborne leaflets], newspapers (???? Gunjin Shinbun; ???? Zensen Gaho; ?????? Minami Taiheiyo Shuho; ?? Jisei; ???? Gunjin Gaho; ???? Heishi no Tomo; ???? Jiji Hodo), and songs, in Japanese, Chinese, and English. English translation and synopsis are attached to most of materials. The propaganda materials were prepared by Allies. Also includes a content list in English compiled by Yoneda. In pocket, Japanese and English booklets are included: ????????: ???????????? Nihon Jinmin Kaiho Renmei: Koryo to Kiyaku Soan oyobi Sonota = Japanese People's Emancipation League: Its Program and Activities. Ed. by ????????? Renmei Soritsu Junbi Iinkai = The Japanese American Committee for Democracy. New York: The Japanese American Committee for Democracy, 1944.
    - Campaign Maps, 1942-1945 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      Three campaign maps of Asia, Burma, and China, with handwritten notes of the USOWI's campaign and battles in English and Japanese.
  - 3.2 Materials Related to Japanese American Military Service, 1942-1993
    Contains materials regarding the U.S. Military recruitment of Japanese Americans, including materials regarding recruitment of Japanese American internees for the U.S. Army's language schools circulated in the Manzanar War Relocation Center, and news clippings and other materials regarding the Office of Strategic Services and the Japanese American military service.
    - US Military Recruitment, 1942-1948 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      Contains an announcement for recruiting Japanese American internees for the U.S. Army's language schools circulated in the Manzanar War Relocation Center, and other documents indicating Yoneda's enlistment of the Army of the United States and his assignments of departments. There are photographs of Yoneda and Lou Goldblatt, ILWU Secretary and Treasures, and of his family taken in the camp. Includes benefit application forms, such as "War saving bond, class A pay reservation application," 'family allowances, and national service life insurance." Also includes a booklet, "Nisei in the War against Japan" by Department of the Interior War Relocation Authority, Washington, D. C., April, 1945, which is a collection of news clippings about Japanese American Nisei soldiers.
    - Office of Strategic Services, 1974-1987 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Contains mainly news clippings on Office of Strategic Services (OSS) members and activities. Correspondence includes letters between Yoneda and Howard Schonberger, a professor of the Department of History, University of Maine at Orono, and incoming Japanese letters from Paul Shinsei Kochi, an OSS Kunming member Okinawan activist. There is a list, "Issei, Nisei, Kibei OSS/OWI WWII Activists," compiled by Yoneda on March 20, 1987, listing names and short description of each OSS member. Also includes English summaries for ?? dentan [= airborne leaflets]; and documents on the Japanese American OSS staff members issued by the OSS in photocopied format.
    - Miscellaneous Materials Regarding the Japanese American Military Service, 1943-1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Includes pamphlets, brochures, and news clippings.
    - Miscellaneous Materials Regarding the Japanese American Military Service, 1980-1993 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      Includes news clippings and other materials.
  - 3.3 Publications by the Military Intelligence Service Association and the Go for Broke, 1966-1992
    Materials issued by the Military Intelligence Service Association of Northern California, Inc. and the Go for Broke, Inc., from 1966 to 1992. Includes periodicals, pamphlets, brochures, and other documents.
    - Materials Issued by the Military Intelligence Service Association of Northern California, Inc., 1966-1991, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Reunion pamphlets, brochures, documents, and correspondence, issued by the Military Intelligence Service Association of Northern California, Inc. There is a roster for 1981 membership of the association.
    - M.I.S. Intelligencer. San Francisco, California, 1970 July-1992 February (Box 17, Folder 2)
      M.I.S. Intelligencer. San Francisco: MIS Association of Northern California, Inc. V. 1, no. 2 (July, 1970)-v. 25, no. 1 (Feb. 1992). Some issues are missing.
    - Update. San Francisco, California, 1985 June-1987 November (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Update. San Francisco,: Go for Broke, Inc. V. 1, no. [1] (June, 1985)-v. 3, no. 6 (Nov. 1987). Some issues are missing. Also includes Yoneda's comments on the issue published in Apr. 1986.
  - 3.4 Materials Related to Exhibitions Featuring Japanese American Soldiers, 1966, 1978-1988
    Photographs of Yoneda's materials exhibited in Japan, exhibition brochures and pamphlets, correspondence, and news clippings. There is also a contract for loan of personal property signed by Yoneda and the curator of the Presidio Army Museum.
    - Materials Related to Exhibitions Featuring Japanese American Soldiers, 1966, 1978-1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 3.5 World War II Propaganda Artifacts, circa 1942-1945
    World War II propaganda buttons, pins, stickers, and ribbons, collected by Yoneda. All items are pasted on a paperboard (44 x 35 cm.).
    - World War II Propaganda Artifacts, circa 1942-1945 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- 4. Manuscripts, Publications, and Lectures, 1923-1994
  Series comprise Yoneda's manuscripts, publications, and an audiotape and transcripts of his lectures and talks. Some folders contain Yoneda's research materials, including his notes, letters, photographs, books, pamphlets, and news clippings. Also includes manuscripts and publications forwarded by individual authors to Yoneda.
  - 4.1 Manuscripts by Yoneda, 1927-1942, 1963-1990
    Comprised primarily of manuscripts and outlines of Yoneda's publications, subject bibliographies and chronologies, interview transcripts, and poems compiled under his various pseudonyms. Most of the manuscripts are accompanied with research materials, including Yoneda's handwritten notes, letters, news clippings, photographs, books, and pamphlets. There is also a list of Yoneda's works and lectures.
    - Autobiography, 1969, 1977, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Biographical sketch complied by Yoneda.
    - Asian Labor History: Outline, 1972, 1976, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Brief outlines of Asian labor history compiled by Yoneda. Titles included: "Brief Outline: Asian Pacific American Labor History"; "Brief Outline: U.S. Asian Labor History"; and "Outline on Asian Labor in U.S.A."
    - History of Japanese and Other Ethnic Cannery Workers in Alaska, 1977 March 1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Yoneda's manuscripts titled as: Brief History of Japanese and Other Ethnic Cannery Workers in Alaska.
    - History of Asian Labor in Hawaii, 1977 January 12, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Yoneda's manuscripts titled as: "Asian Labor History in Hawaii"; "Brief Outline: Asian Labor History in Hawaii"; and "Japanese Labor in Hawaii". Also includes a handwritten note on Hawaii sugar plantations.
    - History of Asian labor in Hawaii: Research Materials (1 of 3), undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Photographs of Japanese sugar plantation workers in Hawaii. Includes photographs of Katsu Goto's grave and former "Olowalu" sugar plantation area.
    - History of Asian Labor in Hawaii: Research Materials (2 of 3), 1942-1987 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - History of Asian Labor in Hawaii: Research Materials (3 of 3), 1942-1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Also includes letters from Jack Kimoto and Kenji Higuchi.
    - ???????? Zaibei Nihonjin Rodoshi = A History of Japanese Labor in the United States, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      A manuscript of: ???????? Zaibei Nihonjin Rodoshi = A History of Japanese Labor in the United States.
    - ??????????? Zaibei Nihonjin Rodosha no Rekishi = History of Japanese Labor in the United States, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      A copy of Yoneda's publication, "???????? ??? Zaibei Nihonjin Rodosha no Rekishi," published in 1967 with his comments for revision.
    - ?????????? Zaibei Nikkei Rodosha no Rekishi = History of Nikkei Labor in the U.S., 1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      A manuscript of the revised edition of: ?????????? Zaibei Nikkei Rodosha no Rekishi = History of Nikkei Labor in the U.S.
    - ????????? Zaibei Nikkeijin Rodoshashi = The Nikkei Labor History in the U.S.A., 1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      A manuscript of the revised edition of: ???????? ? Zaibei Nikkeijin Rodoshashi = The Nikkei Labor History in the U.S.A.
    - History of Japanese Labor in the United States: Research Materials, 1950s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Also includes photographs of I.W.W. strike in San Pedro, 1923.
    - Japanese American History: Research Materials (1 of 2), 1950s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Japanese American History: Research Materials (2 of 2), 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - ???????????? Ichi Nikkeijin Okinakashi no Suto Nikki = Strike Diary, 1971 July 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Yoneda's manuscripts.
    - ?????????????? Ichi Nikkeijin Okinakashi no Hyakunichi Suto Nikki, 1971 November 12 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - ?????????? Kanada Nihonjin Rodo Shoshi, 1963-1975 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Yoneda's manuscripts. Also contains his handwritten notes and news clippings on ???? Tamura Toshiko.
    - Asian Activists during the 60s Civil Rights Movement, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
      A chronological list compiled by Yoneda. Titled as: Among Some Asian Activists During the 60s Civil Rights Movement.
    - Peasant Uprisings in Japan, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      Yoneda's drafts of: "Partial History of Peasant Uprisings in Japan"; "A Chronological Table of the Socialist Movement in Japan"; and "Some Historical Activities of Farmers and Peasants in Japan."
    - Peasant Uprisings in Japan: Research Materials (1 of 3), circa 1972 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      Research materials on ????? Sakura, Sogoro.
    - Peasant Uprisings in Japan: Research Materials (2 of 3), 1971-1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Research materials on ????? oshio, Heihachiro.
    - Peasant uprisings in Japan: Research Materials (3 of 3), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Research materials on ????? Nishimotoya, Buichi.
    - Japanese Radical Heritage, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      A manuscript with research materials.
    - Radical Heritage of the U.S. Japanese, 1978 March 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      "Brief Outline on Radical Heritage of the U.S. Japanese: 1975 to 1951" compiled by Yoneda.
    - Radical Pioneer Japanese Women in U.S., 1920s-1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      Yoneda's manuscripts of "Radical Pioneer Japanese Women in U.S.", his handwritten notes on Japanese women activists in the United States in English and Japanese, and research materials.
    - Political Activities of Japanese Refugees and Japanese Socialists in America, 1965 March 26 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      A manuscript titled as: A Brief Summary of the Political Activities of Japanese Refugees and Japanese Socialists in America (1880-1934).
    - U.S. Japanese Socialists-Communists in the 1930s and 1940s, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Also includes "Brief Outline: U.S. Japanese Socialists-Communists Prior to and during '30s and '40s" and "??????????????? Zaibei Nihonjin Kyosanto ni Kanshite no Ryakushi = A Brief History of U.S. Japanese Communists." There are incoming letters, news clippings and other documents on ???? Nosaka, Sanzo.
    - Mosukuwa de Jukeisareta Rokumei no Issei Kyosan Shugisha = Six Issei Communists Executed in Moscow, 1965, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Photocopies of Yoneda's writing, "???????????????????? Mosukuwa de Jukeisareta Rokumei no Issei Kyosan Shugisha" and its English translation, "Six Issei Communists Executed in Moscow." There are a list of the deportees compiled by Yoneda, documents mailed by Fuji Television Network, Inc. Japan.
    - ???????? Rinchisareta Goto Katsu = The lynching of Katsu Goto in 1889, 1971-1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      Includes Japanese and English manuscripts of "The Lynching of Katsu Goto" and his article in English, "Katsu Goto Lynched: 1989 Will Mark the 100th Anniversary of His Murder!"
    - Sen Katayama, 1970-1982 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Yoneda's writings on Sen Katayama. Includes "Heritage of Sen Katayama"; a chronological table titled: "Sen Katayama"; "Sen Katayama: Issei World Revolutionary: 40th Memorial"; "Sen Katayama: Pioneer Socialist in Japan and Untied States"; and "Brief History of Sen Kayatama's Activities Mainly in the USA."
    - Sen Katayama: Research Materials (1 of 3), 1909-1929 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      Photographs and illustrations of Sen Katayama, with English and Japanese annotations.
    - Sen Katayama: Research Materials (2 of 3), 1916-1919 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Photocopies of articles from a journal, ?? Heimin = The Heimin.
    - Sen Katayama: Research Materials (3 of 3), 1933-1936, 1959-1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - ???? Kotoku Shusui, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      Yoneda's Japanese manuscripts titled: "????????? Kotoku Shusui no Zaibei Jidai" and "????????? Kotoku Shusui no Sanfuranshisuko Jidai." There is incoming correspondence from ??? Fujikawa Yu, ????? Shioda Shobei, and ???? Higuchi Kenji, and ??????????? Kotoku Shusui Zenshu Henshu Iinkai.
    - ???? Kotoku Shusui: Research Materials (1 of 2), 1906-1909 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Includes photographs of ???? Kotoku Shusui and ??? Heiminsha.
    - ???? Kotoku Shusui: Research Materials (2 of 2), 1906-1911, 1933, 1960-1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Pioneer Japanese Language Publications, 1976, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
      A draft of "U.S. Pioneer Japanese Language Publications." There is Yoneda's letter regarding Bunzo Washizu and Kosen Takahashi.
    - Manzanar Diary: March 23rd-December 2nd, 1942, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Outline for Yoneda's publication, "Manzanar Diary," beginning from March 23 through April 8, 1942. Also includes drafts of its introduction and photocopies of camp materials.
    - Sino-Japanese War and World War II Events, 1937-1942 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      Yoneda's handwritten chronological lists including subsequent entries made on Sino-Japanese War and World War II events.
    - Revision, 1989, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
      Yoneda's manuscripts for revision of his publications. Also includes a letter from James Oda.
    - Research Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Yoneda's handwritten research notes on various subjects.
    - Interview Transcripts, 1974 August 8, 1982 April 20 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      Two Yoneda's interview transcripts regarding his World War II experience conducted by Yvonne Yoneda, Yoneda's granddaughter, and regarding President Nixon conducted by Akahata on August 8, 1974.
    - Poems, 1927-1933, 1977-1984 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      Poems compiled by Yoneda under his pseudonyms and Japanese song lyrics with English translation.
    - Bibliographies, circa 1965-1979 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      Subject bibliographies compiled by Yoneda, listing publications on Japanese labor workers in the United States and Canada, communist activities in Japan, etc. The items listed were published from 1888 to 1957, mainly selected from Yoneda's own collection.
    - List of Yoneda's Works and Lectures, 1967-1985 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Book Reviews, Comments, etc., 1965-1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Manuscripts of Yoneda's review articles and letters to publishers. Includes incoming correspondence from Michi Weglyn.
  - 4.2 Publications by Yoneda, 1923-1989
    Comprised of Yoneda's publications, including books, pamphlets, journal articles, and newspaper articles. There is a collection of news clippings including his newspaper articles and poems published from 1923 to 1988 under various pseudonyms, such as ???? Hotta Koji, ?? Hama Kiyoshi, ??? Hama Kiyohi, ?? Yone Tsuyoshi, ???? Yoneda Aika, ???? Karu Hama, etc. There is also a file containing book reviews and announcements about his publications.
    - ??????????? Amerika Joho Heishi no Nikki = A Nikkei M.I.S. Soldier's Diary 1942-1945, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      ?????? Yoneda, Karu. ??????????? Amerika Joho Heishi no Nikki = A Nikkei M.I.S. Soldier's Diary 1942-1945. Tokyo: PMC Shuppan, 1989. In Japanese.
    - ???????????? Manzana Kyosei Shuyojo Nikki = Manzanar Concentration Camp Diary 12/7/41-12/17/42, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      ?????? Yoneda, Karu. ???????????? Manzana Kyosei Shuyojo Nikki = Manzanar Concentration Camp Diary 12/7/41-12/17/42. Tokyo: PMC Shuppan, 1988. In Japanese.
    - Ganbatte: Sixty-Year Struggle of a Kibei Worker, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Yoneda, Karl G. Ganbatte: Sixty-Year Struggle of a Kibei Worker. Los Angeles: Resource Development and Publications Asian American Studies Center, c1983. In English.
    - ?????: ??????60???? Ganbatte: Nikkei Beijin Kakumeika 60-nen no Kiseki, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      ?????? Yoneda, Karu. ?????: ???????60???? Ganbatte: Nikkei Beijin Kakumeika 60-nen no Kiseki. Translated by ????? Tanaka Michiko, ???? Tanaka Reizo. Tokyo: Otsuki Shoten, 1984. In Japanese.
    - ??????????? Amerika Mohitotsu no Kao, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      ?????? Yoneda, Karu. ??????????? Amerika Mohitotsu no Kao. Tokyo: Shin Nihon Shuppansha, 1978. In Japanese.
    - ??????????? Zaibei Nihonjin Rodosha no Rekishi, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      ?????? Yoneda, Karu. ??????????? Zaibei Nihonjin Rodosha no Rekishi. Tokyo: Shin Nihon Shuppansha, 1967. In Japanese.
    - The Heritage of Sen Katayama, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Yoneda, Karl G. The Heritage of Sen Katayama. San Francisco: distributor Book Center, [1975]. A pamphlet includes Yoneda's article reprinted from the March 1975 issue of "Political Affairs, Theoretical Journal of the Communist Party U.S. A." In English.
    - A Brief History of U.S. Asian Labor, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Yoneda, Karl G. A Brief History of U.S. Asian Labor. New York: Political Affairs Reprints, [1976]. A pamphlet includes Yoneda's article reprinted from the September 1976 issue of "Political Affairs, Theoretical Journal of the Communist Party U.S. A." In English.
    - NY?? NY Bungei, 1957-1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Extracts of Yoneda's articles from "NY?? NY Bungei." Also includes news clippings on Yoneda's articles. In Japanese.
    - Journal Articles, 1966-1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      Yoneda's articles published in various journals in English and Japanese.
    - News Clippings (1 of 6), 1923-1935 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Yoneda's newspaper articles and poems published from 1923 to 1935. Mostly in Japanese, with some English.
    - News Clippings (2 of 6), 1946-1955 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Yoneda's newspaper articles published from 1946 to 1955. Mostly in Japanese, with some in English.
    - News Clippings (3 of 6), 1956-1960 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Yoneda's newspaper articles published from 1956 to 1960. Mostly in Japanese, with some in English.
    - News Clippings (4 of 6), 1961-1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Materials are stored in Box 49 (oversize box).
    - News Clippings (5 of 6), 1972-1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Yoneda's newspaper articles published from 1972 to 1979. Also includes some articles written by Elaine Yoneda. In Japanese and English.
    - News Clippings (6 of 6), 1980-1988 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Yoneda's newspaper articles published from 1980 to 1988. In Japanese and English.
    - Book Reviews and Announcement, 1967-1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Book reviews and publication announcements for Yoneda's books. In English and Japanese.
    - News Clippings (4 of 6), 1961-1971 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Yoneda's newspaper articles published from 1961 to 1971. In Japanese and English.
  - 4.3 Lectures and Talks by Yoneda, 1969-1989
    Comprised primarily of transcripts of Yoneda's lectures delivered to classes and programs of various academic institutions on the West Coast and Hawaii, from 1969 to 1989, along with related materials and research materials. There are also files containing transcripts of his talks given at other occasions, such as conferences, annual meetings, symposiums, forums, and the Communist Party, USA events with the materials related to the events. Also includes an audiocassette tape of his lecture, and a list of Yoneda's lectures given at classes and programs at the academic institutions.
    - A List of Lectures Given at Academic Institutions, 1969-1979 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      A list of Yoneda's lectures compiled by Yoneda, documenting the names of the academic institutions, coordinators, dates, number of attendees, and lecture fees.
    - Lectures Outlines, 1970-1983, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Lecture titles include: "100 Years of Japanese Labor in U.S.A."; "Japanese Labor History in U.S.A"; "Asian Labor in the U.S."; "U.S. Asian Labor History"; "U.S. Asian Pacific Americans' Labor History"; "California Asian Farm Labor History"; "Chinese Labor History"; "Japanese Labor and Radical Heritages in USA"; and "Radical Heritage of the U.S. Japanese."
    - History of Japanese Labor in the United States, 1969 February 25-1974 October 22 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      Transcripts of Yoneda's lectures. Titles include: "100 Years of Japanese Labor in the U.S.A"; "A Brief History of Japanese Labor in the USA"; "Japanese Labor History in the United States"; "Japanese Labor Heritage in USA"; and "U.S. Japanese History and Japanese Community."
    - History of Japanese Farm Labor in California, 1969-1981 December 13 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Transcripts of Yoneda's lectures. Titles include: "History of Japanese Labor in California"; "Japanese Farm Labor History in California"; "Japanese Labor Heritage in California"; "A Brief History of U.S. Japanese Labor"; "A Partial History of California Japanese Farm Workers"; and "Japanese Labor and Fascism."
    - History of Japanese Farm Labor in California: Research Materials, 1960-1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Includes photocopies of articles, Yoneda's handwritten notes, and other materials on California agricultural strikes from 1930 to 1936.
    - History of Japanese Labor in Hawaii, 1970 October 27-1971 April 21 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Transcripts of Yoneda's lectures. Titled as: Brief History of Japanese Labor in Hawaii.
    - History of Asian Labor in the United States, 1973 March 22-1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Transcripts of Yoneda's lectures. Titles include: "Asian Labor History in USA"; "Asian Labor in the U.S."; "California Asian Farm Labor History"; "A Brief History of U.S. Asian Labor and Related Events"; "Recent Trends in Asian American Labor Studies"; and "U.S. Asian Labor: Yesterday and Today."
    - Nikkei Radicals and Japanese in the United States, 1972 March 9-1986 May 19 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Transcripts of Yoneda's lectures. Titles include: "Labor and Radical Heritage of Japanese in U.S.A."; "Radical Heritage of U.S. Japanese: 1975 to 1951"; "Nikkei Labor History and Radical Artists"; "Brief California Nikkei Radical and Labor History"; and "Early Radicals Among U.S. Japanese Workers."
    - Chinese and Japanese Labor in the United States, 1969 April 10-15 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      Transcripts of Yoneda's lecture. Titled as: Notes on History of Chinese and Japanese Labor in the U.S.A.
    - Evacuation and Camp Experience, 1971 January 29-1988 February 7 (Box 25, Folder 7)